<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Rich Wells</title>
 <link href="http://richwells.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://richwells.me/"/>
 <updated>2017-03-30T13:24:35+01:00</updated>
 <id>http://richwells.me</id>
 <author>
   <name>Rich Wells</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Back to collage</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/back-to-collage"/>
   <updated>2016-02-12T10:35:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/back-to-collage</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt; It sounds a bit lame, but a big creative highlight of my last year was rediscovering collaging — mainly cutting and sticking bits of paper onto other bits of paper with Pritt Stick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Wake me up slowly&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I think it was probably 1990 where I decided that I’d grown out of ‘cutting and sticking’, and it took having a child and a rainy day in 2015 to rediscover it again. Here are some of my collages from the past year, and a few things I’ve learned from destroying all my magazines.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-2.jpeg&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Making collages chills you out&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I like collaging for the same reason I like drawing — it’s relaxing and enjoyable, and something good to do away from computer screens. The more I stare at my laptop, the less ideas I have, and the more tired I get. It’s interesting seeing all these ‘mindfulness colouring books’ pop up in newsagents. I’m sure collaging has the same affect. I find with collaging I lose track of time, and it gives me energy for other creative pursuits.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-3.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-4.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-5.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;I’ve learned a lot about composition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Having a regular playground to explore different layout ideas has definitely helped my eye for design. I don’t know if I’m a better designer since starting this, but I’m learning a lot more about what I like and how my brain works. There’s a real freedom in being able to move shapes around until they make something that feels right, and then to think why that feels right. When I’m collaging I generally keep things fluid and stick everything down at the end. Sometimes I’ll add loads of elements, and then take everything away to it’s simplest form. And sometimes I just throw it all away.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-6.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-7.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;It’s helped me to work quicker&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I don’t spend a long time making collages. Often I set a 10 minute timer, which removes the pressure to make something perfect. I often go with my first instinct, or I cut out an interesting shape and go on from there.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-8.jpeg&quot;&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Collaging is a form of remixing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  There’s a great video series online called “Everything is a Remix.” I like that title—it’s so true, there are very few original things (or people) out there. The work most of us create is either inspired by the people around us, our environments, or the work of other people. Collaging is pure remixing—you ‘sample’ existing things and combine them together to build something new that didn’t exist before.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-9.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-10.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;People start giving you magazines and flyers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I was very blessed to be given a whole bin liner full of National Geographics, which I’m making my way through. I’m reading them first, so it’s taking a while.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-11.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-12.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-13.jpeg&quot;&gt;



&lt;h2&gt;You make a lot of mess and it can be a strain on a relationship&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Thankfully I have a gracious wife. I also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/5ynjXXlgxh/&quot;&gt;built a shed &lt;/a&gt; last year to contain all the mess (but that’s the subject for another blog post).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-14.jpeg&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;I enjoyed it so much I made it part of my routine&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I wake up fairly early in the week so I can have a bit of time to read/think/pray/create before life starts. Because it gives me energy, I’ve made collaging a habit, spending 10 minutes every morning making something quick, just for fun. Sometimes I share them online (with the hashtag #morningcollage—not sure why), sometimes I don’t.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-15.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-16.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-17.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-18.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h2&gt;You should give it a go&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  You don’t need a mac, or any expensive software. If like me, you haven’t collaged since your youth (why would you?), pick it up again! It’s cheap, fun, and doesn’t hurt anyone (depending on your scissor skills).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Also it’s a good childminding activity. I made this Christmas collage last year with some kids at our church, and they all seemed to enjoy it more than me.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids&quot;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/147464564&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; height=&quot;281&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-19.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-20.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-21.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-22.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-25.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-23.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-26.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-24.jpeg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/collage-27.jpeg&quot;&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Sheffield Digital</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/sheffield-digital"/>
   <updated>2016-01-27T10:35:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/sheffield-digital</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sheffield Digital logo&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt; I recently had the pleasure of designing the identity for Sheffield Digital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The organisation was set up a year ago by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@chrisdymond&quot; data-href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@chrisdymond&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Chris&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@melkanarek&quot; data-href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@melkanarek&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Mel&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@saulcozens&quot; data-href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@saulcozens&quot;rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Saul&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@birchenall&quot; data-href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@birchenall&quot;&gt;Neill&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@andymayer&quot; data-href=&quot;https://twitter.com/@andymayer&quot;&gt;Andy&lt;/a&gt;, to connect people together in Sheffield, be a voice for the community and promote the city’s digital capabilities around the country/world.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Workshopping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  We got started by running a brand workshop at Yoomee HQ. To get everyone talking about design, we laid out a heat map of images/designs/messaging that we thought fitted with where we wanted to go. Often the most interesting part of these workshops are the disagreements — the tension between “it’s this, but also this, but definitely not that.” We all come from different angles and sometimes we don’t have the right words to explain what we mean, so having visual examples and time to thrash out a shared direction really helps.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-workshop.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brand workshop at Yoomee&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Our heat map ended up becoming a bit of a moodboard. We were inspired by patterns, glitches, maps, and things that felt digital without looking too ‘techy’ or ‘Broadband ISP’.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-moodboard.jpg&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot; alt=&quot;Moodboard&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Early ideas&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I started playing around with a few logo ideas, some more wacky than others. I was keen to keep the logo simple, over the top of more creative colours/patterns.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-ideas.jpg&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot; alt=&quot;early ideas&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-gif.gif&quot; alt=&quot;early logo ideas&quot; class=&quot;small&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  We eventually landed on a concept, inspired by maps. An abstract shape showing connections in the city.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-map.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Network pattern inspired by maps&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The logo in itself is really simple, says what it does (the url is sheffield.digital). I used the excellent font Calibre, and slightly altered some of the letter forms so the ‘h and d’ and the two ‘l’s aligned.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-logo-grid.png&quot; alt=&quot;refining the logo&quot; class=&quot;small&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  We ended up picking a range of colours, half inspired by text editors and half inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;http://sheffield.digital/announcing-the-sheffielddigital-slack-team/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Slack’s&lt;/a&gt; colourful UI. As Slack is heavily used by the Sheffield Digital community (and us at &lt;a href=&quot;http://yoomee.com&quot;&gt;Yoomee&lt;/a&gt;), it seemed like a good idea to have a colour scheme that compliments that. I also designed some obligatory non digital things.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-tshirts.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tshirts and twitter&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I worked with Saul on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://sheffield.digital&quot;&gt;responsive Wordpress site&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a quick first iteration, and we hope to develop it over time.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sd-website.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sheffield Digital Website&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot;&gt;

&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I also posted this to &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@richwells/sheffield-digital-b4665e87c1d2#.3vkq9fnho&quot;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Designing a plywood sofa</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/designing-a-plywood-sofa"/>
   <updated>2015-11-27T10:35:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/designing-a-sofa</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Plywood sofa&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt; When deciding what side projects to take up, I pick things that are different to what I do normally in the day, and challenge me in some kind of new way. A while back we needed a sofa at work and so it sounded like a good challenge to make one. “How hard can it be?” I said. (Well, quite, it turns out).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; The inspiration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-original.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Eames Sofa Compact&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  One of my favourite chairs is the Eames sofa compact, designed by Charles and Ray Eames in 1954. When it came out it was pretty revolutionary. They wanted to create “The best for the least, for the most,” and before flat pack furniture became the norm they designed a chair that could be shipped in a small box and assembled by anyone. They knew that shipping carriers preferred weight over volume, and so they started with that constraint — something that could be shipped anywhere cheaply and wouldn’t get damaged in the process.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-box.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Unpacking an Eames Sofa&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-box-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Unpacking an Eames Sofa&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;
  The Sofa compact is simple with just three cushions and a frame, but to get there, the Eames explored many different prototypes with a variety of materials and angles, until they got to something that is incredible comfy and takes up a small amount of space.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-s73.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-s73-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;
  I’d like to own an Eames Sofa one day, but as I don’t have a spare $5000 lying around I decided to design something for myself inspired by it, out of plywood.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Early ideas&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Here are some of my initial sketches/ideas.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-sketches.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Initial sketches&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided before spending money on plywood I should make some 3D models on my computer to work out how much plywood I would need. I used &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sketchup.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Sketch Up&lt;/a&gt; (it’s free) and started with a simple three cushion shape and a supporting plywood base.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-sketchup-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sketch up prototypes&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot;&gt;


&lt;h2&gt; Refining the design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
I liked where it was going, but it was pretty brutal in shape. Over time I refined the legs and the back- taking material away whilst thinking about the weight it needed to support. I wanted it to feel mid-century modern- clean, with slightly tapered legs and no harsh edges.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-sketchup-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sketch up prototypes&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Details, details&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It was starting to come together, but there were still lots of details I needed to sort out. The main one being: How would it be strong enough to hold three people’s weight?
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
At one point I was considering attaching steel bars to the frame, but I really wanted it to be elegant and strong enough to work it’s own, so I designed a supporting frame that the base could slot on to, to distribute the weight onto the legs.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-frame.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The frame&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Designing for assembly&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
The design was getting quite complex and I knew that I would struggle to make it myself. It was around this point that I discovered &lt;a href=&quot;http://chopshopcnc.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;The Chop Shop&lt;/a&gt; — a company in Sheffield that will cut out any shape you want in plywood. This changed my thinking - rather than design a one off for myself I started to consider how I could design the sofa for others to cut out and assemble.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
On the screen I worked out how I would put this together from the separate parts. If everything was to slot together it was really important to make it as obvious as possible where each bit goes, and so I either tried to make part exactly the same or completely different to avoid any confusion.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-exploded-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The sofa exploded&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-exploded-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The sofa exploded&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Exporting the design &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Now the design was ready to be cut out. I exported the parts (using the free &lt;a href=&quot;https://extensions.sketchup.com/en/content/wikihouse&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Wikihouse&lt;/a&gt; plugin) to svg vectors, which I could then lay out on a board in Illustrator. I eventually had three boards, with a bit of space on them to play around with other ideas.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-boards.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The sofa parts layed out on a board&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Chop Shopping &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
We were finally ready to go. My first design was cut out late on a Friday evening by Sam at the Chop Shop. The finished result was a bit like a giant airfix model.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-chopshop-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;At the chop shop&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-chopshop-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;At the chop shop&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-chopshop-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;At the chop shop&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-chopshop-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;At the chop shop&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It was so weird holding the actual parts after working through all the details for so long on a screen. They seemed smaller than I imagined and I was pretty nervous that this would all be a failure, that my 10 months of thinking/designing (admittedly whilst watching tv) would have been a waste. I still didn’t really know if it would hold a person’s weight.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Assembling the frame &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
To my joy and relief- it worked! I put together the wooden frame in our front room and it felt really sturdy and I was especially pleased with the angles of the back. There were a few tight slots that needed filing out, but all in all it worked as expected.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-living-room.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Assemling it all&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Upholstery &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
I got the cushions upholstered by a local shop called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cundys.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Cundy upholstery&lt;/a&gt;. They’re pretty old school, so I had to convert all my measurements to inches, but they gave me some really helpful advice.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-cundys.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cundy upholstery&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Getting the back cushions right was essential for the design to work, so we developed a way of using multiple layers of foam to get the right shape. The foam was covered in a dacron wrap, and then the fabric was added on top, stapled to a thin board which was screwed to the back boards.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt; Putting it all together &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
So the day finally came around where I could assemble everything, which I did in our office. Everyone stopped work to watch me nervously attach everything together and be the first guinea pig to test it out. I think they were secretly hoping I&#39;d squash it.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-cushion.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The sofa back boards&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-straps.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The sofa straps&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; So what’s it like to sit on? &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
To my relief it works much better than I even imagined. It’s fairly firm at the moment, it’s not a “cuddle up and watch tv” sofa, but having used it a lot for a week, it’s the perfect angle for reading and using laptops, and it’s already starting to soften up. The most rewarding thing has been seeing other people use it in the team- it’s changed a corner of the room we didn’t use into a social area, and made our temporary office space feel a lot more like home.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-mark.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mark sitting on the sofa&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sofa-group.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Group sitting on the sofa&quot;&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Next steps &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
I want to treat this project like I would a digital one — I have a first version but it needs testing, and I want to learn as much as I can and build further iterations to improve the design. I already have a list of things I want to improve (mainly around making it easy to assemble), so hopefully I can iron out a few ‘bugs’ before I give it to the world.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Still not sure what to do with it in the end - I’m considering open sourcing the design so other people can make them too. I’ll  let you know how I go.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;H3&gt;Big thanks to&lt;/H3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;My wife Bry for her patience&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yoomee for paying for the first prototype and letting me work on this in &#39;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoomee.com/investment-time&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;investment time&lt;/a&gt;&#39;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ivan &amp;amp; Sam at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://chopshopcnc.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Chop Shop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cundys.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Cundy Upholstery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Barbican, for their excellent exhibition: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.barbican.org.uk/artgallery/event-detail.asp?ID=18398&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;&quot;The World of Charles and Ray Eames&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  I also posted this to &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@richwells/building-a-plywood-sofa-c30882f50bf5#.n0j890d95&quot;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Never a grey day</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/never-grey"/>
   <updated>2015-11-18T10:35:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/never-grey</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/nevergrey.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;never a grey day when I&#39;m with you&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  When I think of Manchester and the time I spent living there, I often remember the grey skies and the rain. Oh and the wind. And sleet in the winter. I also remember the friendly people, inspiring streets and a creative buzz, especially around the northern quater.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I started this picture 10 years ago, a mix of acrylics and spray paint that stank out my small flat and made me feel a bit dizzy, probably contributing to the warped view of the Manchester skyline that I ended up painting. I finished it the other day by adding the letters, carved out of lino and printed from the comfort &amp;amp; fresh air of my garden shed. I’m turning into a proper old man…
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Square Share</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/squareshare"/>
   <updated>2015-07-20T11:35:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/square-share</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  Two of my friends Matt and Tom recently started up a business called &lt;a href=&quot;http://square-share.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Square Share&lt;/a&gt; and I helped them set up their branding.
&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img class=&quot;small&quot; src=&quot;/downloads/ss-matt-and-tom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tom and Matt&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  The Square Share idea came about after an art installation they made called &lt;em&gt;The selfie printer&lt;/em&gt;, which pulls through all #selfie images in real time on Twitter and Instagram, and prints them out quickly on a receipt printer. The printer would be left on for weeks in a room, filling up the floor and walls with pictures of people’s faces from all around the world.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;4&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:50% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAAGFBMVEUiIiI9PT0eHh4gIB4hIBkcHBwcHBwcHBydr+JQAAAACHRSTlMABA4YHyQsM5jtaMwAAADfSURBVDjL7ZVBEgMhCAQBAf//42xcNbpAqakcM0ftUmFAAIBE81IqBJdS3lS6zs3bIpB9WED3YYXFPmHRfT8sgyrCP1x8uEUxLMzNWElFOYCV6mHWWwMzdPEKHlhLw7NWJqkHc4uIZphavDzA2JPzUDsBZziNae2S6owH8xPmX8G7zzgKEOPUoYHvGz1TBCxMkd3kwNVbU0gKHkx+iZILf77IofhrY1nYFnB/lQPb79drWOyJVa/DAvg9B/rLB4cC+Nqgdz/TvBbBnr6GBReqn/nRmDgaQEej7WhonozjF+Y2I/fZou/qAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/p/pYq8Hwlg0T/&quot; style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;&quot; target=&quot;_top&quot;&gt;A video posted by Rich Wells (@richwells)&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;time style=&quot; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&quot; datetime=&quot;2014-06-18T12:31:10+00:00&quot;&gt;Jun 18, 2014 at 5:31am PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async defer src=&quot;//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Seeing the selfie printer in action made me think a lot about the things we share online and how people might engage with them in ways we couldn’t imagine. And also how vain we can be sometimes! The art project had a huge response and they decided to develop the idea further.

&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;img class=&quot;small&quot; src=&quot;/downloads/ss-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;#selfie to #yourevent&quot;&gt;


&lt;p&gt;
  The result was Square Share. Photos pulled in realtime from social media and printed instantly, on high quality photo paper. They were inspired by how disposable cameras at weddings give a different angle on the day and how physical polaroid prints change the way people interact with photos.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;square-share&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot; /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  When Matt first showed me the prototype I was really impressed with the simple box they’d made to house the printer,  Raspberry Pi and internet dongle that made it work. While the #selfie art project had all the wires on show, the Square Share box was clean, simple and a bit magical. It reminded me of early Apple products - hiding the technical stuff and making something more human and fun. It was great to see how people responded with surprise and joy to a photo they’d just shared online coming out of a random box, at hand height.

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;inspiration and thoughts&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  I realised that the box and the prints were the most important elements of the brand. The design and branding shouldn’t get in the way of this, so I decided to keep it as simple as possible. I ended up choosing three colours, and a nice rounded font for the titles to give it that human feel. After exploring a few different logo ideas and trying to be clever with printer icons and animations, I stripped everything away and put their name in a box. Simple. Here are some pages from my brand guidelines.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;lgoo guidelines&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;colours&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;typography&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;photo print&quot;&gt;


&lt;!-- &lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; --&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;t-shirt&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;website&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ss-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Square Share in action&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot;&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Be kind to your future self</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/be-kind-to-your-future-self"/>
   <updated>2015-05-20T11:35:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/be-kind-to-your-future-self</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/be-kind-to-your-future-self-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;be kind to your future self illustration&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I&#39;ve been experimenting with a bit of linoprinting. A few months ago my sister gave me some spare tools and I&#39;ve been messing around with simple shapes every now and then. This is my first attempt at a proper print. The phrase comes from my colleague David, and I thought it&#39;d be a nice gift for him as he moves on to a new job.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  There&#39;s something about cutting lino (or fake primary school lino in this case) that&#39;s really satisfying. Maybe it&#39;s to do with being offscreen and it taking time to see the results. I had to be a bit strategic with lino as I was running out, so I stuck it to some cardboard and it seemed to work. I have no idea what I&#39;m doing!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/be-kind-to-your-future-self-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;the lino&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  After trying a few prints my favourites are the ones that are slightly washed out and distorted. It gives it a bit more character.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/be-kind-to-your-future-self.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;blue version of the illustration&quot;&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Daddy Daycare</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/farewell-to-the-daddy-daycare-blog"/>
   <updated>2015-05-05T11:35:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/farewell-daddy-daycare-blog</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  After nearly two years and 75 blog posts I’ve decided to stop posting to my &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Daddy daycare blog&lt;/a&gt;. It’s the end of a (very happy) blogging era. I’m still taking Tuesdays off with Sophie but the blog will be no more.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  “But why?” I hear you say (If you happen to follow it and happen to be bothered).
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/farewell-daddy-daycare-intro.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;farewell daddy daycare montage&quot; &gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  There are a few reasons, but I think the main one is that Sophie is no longer a ‘generic looking baby’. She’s morphed, much quicker than expected, into a little girl with wild curly hair who eats more breakfast than her mum and talks all the time and and can write herself (well, ‘m’ for mummy, so early days). It’s starting to feel a bit odd, me pretending to write in her voice when she has one of her own now.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  But more importantly, as a dad I’m starting to feel a bit uneasy sharing so many pictures of her online in public, now that she’s a lot more recognisable. I’m not a paranoid person when it comes to online security, and I’ve been careful to not share any ‘this is our house’ photos, but I’m also aware that you can build a picture of what Sophie’s like and where we live by looking at posts over time, and I’ve had a nagging feeling in the back of my mind when blogging recently, which is probably a good sign that it’s time to stop.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;A bit of history&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  I started the daddy daycare blog back in 2013, just as I switched to working part time. It was a challenge to myself, to do something new every week, get out of the house, explore our surroundings and share with family what we got up to in the day.     It’s definitely made life more fun, enjoyable and interesting.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  I didn’t expect that so many people would follow along and respond like they have done. Something that I thought only my mum would read has ended up becoming checked by lots of people every week, more than I know personally. It’s opened up lots of doors for me, from conversations to travel opportunities and giving talks in different places. And having a regular rhythm of  writing (something I really struggle with) has been great, along with editing and ordering photos at speed on my phone whilst cooking tea. I’ve loved it.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;What next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  As I said earlier, I’m still taking Tuesdays off with Sophie, and we’ll still go on adventures. I think I’ll keep the blog online for a bit, and then I’ll probably take it down and make a photo book that we can look at when we’re old and wrinkly.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Enjoyed reading the daddy daycare blog? Let me know! It’s always good to be encouraged:-)
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Digital Disciples</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/digital-disciples"/>
   <updated>2015-02-15T10:35:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/digital-disciples-talk</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;//www.slideshare.net/slideshow/embed_code/44710518&quot; width=&quot;720&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Last weekend I did a talk at The Student Conference in Sheffield, an event for 100 or so Christian students at the Showroom Cinema. I shared a bit about me and a few thoughts on technology, faith, storytelling and the internet. Here are some of my slides.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;a class=&quot;cta&quot; href=&quot;http://goo.gl/k04Fhj&quot;&gt;Download slides as a PDF&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/dd-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Improving Google Tasks</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/blog/better-google-tasks"/>
   <updated>2014-11-22T10:35:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/blog/better-google-tasks</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’m kind of in love with Todo lists, which is a bit sad really. I make lists all the time and love ticking things off. Sometimes I write things that I’ve already done, just to put a line through it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/bgt-completed.jpg&quot; class=&quot;small&quot; alt=&quot; Write a blog post (completed)&quot; /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried most of the popular todo list apps out there and the one I keep coming back to is Google Tasks. It’s simple, free, saves to my Gmail account so I don’t need to log into anything else, and it works with loads of different mobile apps, meaning my tasks are everywhere and always synced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trouble is, there’s no decent looking way of using Google Tasks in a desktop browser. This is their curent design:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/bgt-before.jpg&quot; class=&quot;small&quot; alt=&quot; The current Google Tasks&quot; /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Google stopped developing their tasks browser app a few years ago and it looks pretty dated now. Not a great thing to look at for long periods of time (which I do as I use it for work).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to add my own styles on top of Google Tasks, just for me really. I wanted to make a thing I stare at every day better and easier to use. I took away some of the noise, made certain things more  clear and legible and generally made it more satisfying to check off tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/better-google-tasks.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Better Google Tasks&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot; /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve had a few iterations of the design. The earlier versions looked a lot more impressive, but then I realised that I needed to make something that I didn&#39;t notice. This isn&#39;t a site homepage, it&#39;s a tool, and the important thing is that I can clearly see what I need to do and when I need to do it.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/bgt-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Better Google Tasks&quot; class=&quot;wide&quot; /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I probably spent most time styling the completed tasks. I wanted to make it feel satisfying and instant to check stuff off, so I removed images that might take some time to load and made CSS checkboxes (which look much sharper on retina screens too).
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/bgt-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot; The current Google Tasks&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/bgt-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Better Google Tasks&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s still a work in progress, the code is pretty horrible and there are loads of things I’d like to improve, but it’s a bit better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My friend &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/matkins&quot;&gt;Matt&lt;/a&gt; turned my styles into a browser extension, which was very kind of him. If you use Google Chrome you can have it for free here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/better-google-tasks/denjcdefjebbmlihdoojnebochnkgcin&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;Download Better Google Tasks&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Want to find out more about this project? &lt;a href=&quot;http://richwells.me/better-google-tasks/&quot;&gt; Here&#39;s a little brochure/help site&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Picture frame coffee table</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/picture-frame-coffee-table"/>
   <updated>2014-11-21T10:35:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/picture-frame-coffee-table</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/picture-frame-coffee-table-tn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot; picture frame coffee table&quot; /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A paternity leave project. This small coffee table started out as two oak IKEA RIBBA picture frames and some wood offcuts. When it’s not in use, it hides away neatly under our sofa. I also put a slide out drawer underneath to store pens for a certain four year old artist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/picture-frame-1.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/picture-frame-2.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/picture-frame-3.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Making a Christmas film</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/christmas-film"/>
   <updated>2014-11-21T10:35:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/christmas-film</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/113002294&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; height=&quot;281&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On our &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/post/103027376628/christmas-video&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;daddy daycare&lt;/a&gt; day this week we made a Christmas video with a few friends from Church. It felt a little odd to be singing carols outside in November, but it turned out to be lots of fun. Here are a few screenshots of the things I filmed. Video edited by the super talented &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/leadoutdan&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Dan Harris&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/christmas-film-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;christmas video stills&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Blessed</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/blessed-are-those-who-mourn"/>
   <updated>2014-10-10T11:35:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/blessed-are-those-who-mourn</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/blessed-are-those-who-mourn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cardboard man&quot; class=&quot;&quot;/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of illustrations I did for one of Bry&#39;s talks at church. Enjoyed making things out of paper, just for the fun of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/blessed-are-those-who-mourn-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Verse illustration&quot; class=&quot;&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Four Knows of Creativity</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/the-four-knows-of-creativity"/>
   <updated>2014-09-15T09:09:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/the-four-knows-of-creativity</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; height=&quot;536&quot; marginheight=&quot;0&quot; marginwidth=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;//www.slideshare.net/slideshow/embed_code/39096666&quot; width=&quot;662&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Last weekend I did a talk at the Tearfund Rhythms Visual Communication day. I shared a bit of my story and a few things that I&amp;#8217;ve found helpful to know when creating and communicating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was great to be part of the day and to chat about creativity with some really inspiring young people. There&amp;#8217;s a bit of a transcript thing on my &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.slideshare.net/richiewells/four-knowsofcreativity&quot; title=&quot;Rich Wells slideshare presentation&quot;&gt;slideshare&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Sketches of Spain</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/sketches-of-spain"/>
   <updated>2014-09-09T01:39:44+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/sketches-of-spain</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few sketches and iPad doodles from a week away in Mallorca.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sketches-of-spain-1.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sketches-of-spain.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sketches-of-spain-2.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sketches-of-spain-3.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Festival of Code</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/festival-of-code"/>
   <updated>2014-07-28T19:16:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/festival-of-code</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  This week we welcomed 13 young people and 5 mentors to Electric Works for the Festival of Code. We were one of a number of centres across the country hosting this week-long event which enables young people to get together, form teams, and design and build apps, websites, games or hardware all based around the Government&#39;s open data.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Here&#39;s Tumblr blog I made to keep track of what we got up to: &lt;a href=&quot;http://festivalofcode.tumblr.com/&quot;&gt;http://festivalofcode.tumblr.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yrs.jpg&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yrs-1.gif&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yrs-7.jpg&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yrs-5.png&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#39;fitvids&#39;&gt;
      &lt;iframe src=&#39;//player.vimeo.com/video/102142593&#39; width=&#39;500&#39; height=&#39;281&#39; frameborder=&#39;0&#39; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yrs-4.jpg&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yrs-3.jpg&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/festival-of-code.gif&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yrs-8.jpg&quot;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yrs-2.gif&quot;&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Stretch O' Clock</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/stretch-o-clock"/>
   <updated>2014-07-25T11:35:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/stretch-o-clock</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/stretch-o-clock-2.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My colleague &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/matkins&quot;&gt;Matt&lt;/a&gt; is probably the cleverest person I know, and a nice guy too. Today is his last day at Yoomee before moving on to bigger and better things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aside from insane coding skills, Matt&amp;#8217;s biggest legacy is teaching us some stretch moves that we do as a team every morning at 11am. We started them after reading a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.diygenius.com/your-desk-job-is-killing-you-the-truth-about-sitting-down-infographic/&quot;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; about how sitting at a computer is killing you. Turns out we&amp;#8217;re not designed to be sitting all day hunched over a screen! Now stretching is part of our daily routine and is a good chance to stop, clear your head and talk to each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a leaving gift I made Matt a little framed print celebrating Stretch O’Clock.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A summer of cycling</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/summer-of-cycling"/>
   <updated>2014-07-09T19:16:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/summer-of-cycling</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;ve always been into bicycles, even before they were cool and Britain started winning things on them (not any more mind you thanks to the cobbles). I&amp;#8217;ve watched the Tour de France every year since I was a kid and have fond memories of huddling round our TV with pitiful Channel 4 reception trying to pick out riders from the white noise (no chance when it was raining!). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo10_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watching The Tour pass through Yorkshire last weekend was incredible. It was like having the World Cup come to your local park - so great to watch a major sporting event happen on the familiar roads of the Peak District and brilliant to see how the whole of Yorkshire got behind it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo9_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo7_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hendos Strong &amp; Northern</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/hendersons-strong-and-northern"/>
   <updated>2014-07-09T19:16:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/hendersons-strong-and-northern</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n8gwnoDs491rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To celebrate the Tour coming up north I did a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thelevelcollective.co.uk/shop/strong-and-northern/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;T-shirt design&lt;/a&gt; for the Level Collective, in collaboration with the legendary Sheffield company &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hendersonsrelish.com/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Henderson&#39;s relish&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#8217;re nearly sold out but have a few left in stock &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thelevelcollective.co.uk/shop/strong-and-northern/&quot; title=&quot;Strong and Northern by Rich Wells&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Team Yoomee</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/good-to-be-back"/>
   <updated>2014-05-13T09:47:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/good-to-be-back</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I decided to have a bit of a break from sharing things last month after the intensity of blogging on the move in Cambodia (110 posts in 2 weeks!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s been great to spend some &lt;a href=&#39;http://instagram.com/p/nDyHQVlg3m/&#39;&gt;quality time with family&lt;/a&gt; over Easter, &lt;a href=&#39;http://instagram.com/p/nLg_6llg2v/&#39;&gt;ride bicycles&lt;/a&gt; and get back into my job at Yoomee — we&amp;#8217;ve hired some more people, &lt;a href=&#39;http://instagram.com/p/m5ZcM_lg7j/&#39;&gt;knocked down a wall&lt;/a&gt; and started some exciting &lt;a href=&#39;http://digital.girlguiding.org.uk/introducing-yoomee&#39;&gt;new projects&lt;/a&gt;. Here&amp;#8217;s a little doodle of our current team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#39;team yoomee&#39; src=&#39;http://richwells.me/img/team-yoomee.png&#39;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Cambodia travel scrapbook</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/cambodia-scrapbook"/>
   <updated>2014-03-25T13:24:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/cambodia-scrapbook</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
  Here are a few sketches and iPad paintings from my Cambodian travels last March. I was keen to capture as much as I could and share short stories of the people we met out there.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://cambodia.richwells.me&quot; class=&quot;cta&quot;&gt;View the full travel scrapbook&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/scrapbook-1.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/scrapbook-2.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/scrapbook-3.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/scrapbook-4.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/scrapbook-5.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/scrapbook-6.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/scrapbook-7.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/scrapbook-8.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Our time in Tonle Batie</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/tonle-batie"/>
   <updated>2014-03-23T14:42:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/tonle-batie</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#8217;ve just come back from a two day trip to Tonle Batie, a village an hour or so out of Phnom Penh. No wifi, no 3G, and a great opportunity to spend quality time with some generous people who don&amp;#8217;t always have it easy.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://ir0.mobify.com/300/http://richwells.me/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2wjyiYje51rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://ir0.mobify.com/300/http://richwells.me/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2wjyiYje51rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://ir0.mobify.com/300/http://richwells.me/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2wjyiYje51rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tearfund works with the local church in this community and produces regular video updates in its &amp;#8216;See for Yourself&amp;#8217; video series. Worth a watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids&quot;&gt;
  &lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/vQyQ4XHajCM&quot; width=&quot;800&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Danny and I stayed with Pastor Ke Pich and his family (who is featured in the video above), and I had my first opportunity to sleep under the stars (in a mosquito net). I slept like a baby and was blown away by their hospitality over the weekend. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2wjyiYje51rr6vpvo7_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Had a bit of a nightmare when I got back when I realised that my camera wouldn&amp;#8217;t load the photos onto my mac. Thought I&amp;#8217;d lost them all, but after 2 hours of fiddling I&amp;#8217;ve managed to find a way round it (turns out it was a broken lead, phew!). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;ll be posting stories from Tonle Batie over the next couple of days to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cambodia.richwells.me&quot;&gt;my scrapbook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://ir0.mobify.com/600/http://richwells.me/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2wjyiYje51rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tonle-batie.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://ir0.mobify.com/600/http://richwells.me/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2wjyiYje51rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2wjyiYje51rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Also, please consider giving to Tearfund so that more villages like Tonle Batie can be supported to help themselves out of poverty. £3/month isn&amp;#8217;t very much, and you can even pay quickly and easily by text. I think it&amp;#8217;s such a great cause and have decided to give away 60 art prints to the first people who give. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.richwells.me/post/80255761189/give&quot; title=&quot;Give to Tearfund&quot;&gt;Find out more&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Yoomee.com</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/yoomee-dot-com"/>
   <updated>2014-03-14T16:31:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/yoomee-dot-com</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/yoomee-site.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;yoomee.com&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the frustrations of having so much work on at the moment is that we have little time to update our site. The other week we had a small window in between projects and managed to push a few changes. More to come!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://yoomeee.com&quot; class=&quot;cta&quot;&gt;Visit yoomee.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video-container wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video id=&quot;bgvid&quot; muted=&quot;&quot; autoplay=&quot;&quot; loop=&quot;&quot; poster=&quot;/downloads/yoomee-poster.jpg&quot;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/downloads/yoomee.webm&quot;  type=&quot;video/webm&quot; codecs=&quot;vp8,vorbis&quot;&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
    &lt;source src=&quot;/downloads/yoomee.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; codecs=&quot;avc1.42E01E&quot;&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hey, look I made a toy kitchen!</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/wooden-kitchen"/>
   <updated>2014-03-13T06:41:47+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/wooden-kitchen</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2df1nc2qi1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last Christmas we were going to buy our daughter Sophie a toy Kitchen. She loves anything kitchen related, and we needed somewhere to store her ever growing collection of fake food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As it was going to be in our front room I didn&amp;#8217;t want a garish pink one (why are they always pink?) and the wooden ones in John Lewis were quite expensive so I decided to make my own. &amp;#8216;Easy&amp;#8217; I thought. How wrong I was — I spent far too long in our cellar stooped over a work bench sanding things, sawing things, staining things and inhaling wood dust. And I loved it. It felt really good to make something with my hands and spend some quality time being creative away from a screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2df1nc2qi1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2df1nc2qi1rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big thanks to my mate Duncan Payne for the loan of man tools, and to my wife Bry for her patience!  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2df1nc2qi1rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n2df1nc2qi1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Summer</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/summer"/>
   <updated>2014-03-12T03:12:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/summer</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/summer.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Goldddigger live art auction</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/golddigger-artwork"/>
   <updated>2014-03-11T03:12:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/golddigger-artwork</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Last weekend I did some live art for an organisation called Golddigger Trust. They were having a Charity auction to raise money for the work that they do with young people in our area who need help and support, particularly with self-esteem issues.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At first when I was asked to do this, I was going to say no — two and a half hours to produce something that people would want to buy at the end of the night is pretty daunting. What if I made a mistake? What if I stood there at the front and no one wanted to buy it? But after some thought I decided to do it anyway — it&amp;#8217;s good to do things that scare you sometimes! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n29g1mDevZ1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n29g1mDevZ1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n29g1mDevZ1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to paint something around the story of David and Goliath, the classic underdog story from the Bible. David is this pretty insignificant guy who gets left behind to look after the sheep, but actually has more courage and confidence than anyone else in the Israelite army. I think David had a confidence in who he was made to be because he knew that he was loved and known by God. What a difference it makes when we know someone cares about us and thinks we can do it!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n29g1mDevZ1rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The artwork was due to be auctioned at 10:30pm, but unfortunately everything was running a few minutes early, which meant me squeezing through to the front with a canvas and framing it as it was being sold. Nothing like a bit of drama to the end of the night! I was really blown away by how many bids came in, and it eventually went for £310, not bad for a couple of hours&amp;#8217; work!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#8217;s a short time-lapse video of me working during the evening:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; height=&quot;710&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;//instagram.com/p/lTesL-lg2v/embed/&quot; width=&quot;612&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Tom</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/tom"/>
   <updated>2014-03-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/tom</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n22lmjnjV11rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is Tom, our current apprentice at Yoomee. We&amp;#8217;re starting a scheme to teach young offenders to code, which is a really exciting and rewarding thing to be part of. &lt;a href=&quot;http://yoomee.com/teaching-young-offenders-to-code-update&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Read More about it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Yoomee is hiring</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/yoomee-is-hiring"/>
   <updated>2014-02-13T10:18:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/yoomee-is-hiring</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_n0xx6pbcA01rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Getting the right people on the bus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recruitment for us is about carefully growing a family, taking on board people with potential, and growing, moving forward together as equals. It&amp;#8217;s about getting the right people on the bus first, and then figuring out where to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#8217;re currently looking to hire a designer and developer. Want to work on rewarding projects as part of a brilliant team?  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.yoomee.com/we-are-recruiting&quot; title=&quot;Yoomee is recruiting&quot;&gt;Join us!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Coffee packet typography</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/coffee-packets"/>
   <updated>2014-01-13T18:55:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/coffee-packets</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/coffee-packets.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;After collecting coffee packets for the last 5 years (not really sure why), I have decided to do something creative with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is my first ever coffee packet typeface. I cut each one out by hand and covered my room with stale coffee grounds - it was a labour of love! It&amp;#8217;s early days (there aren&amp;#8217;t any numerals or punctuation yet), but you can download the images for free here. Make something! (I&amp;#8217;d love to know what you come up with).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://goo.gl/KuuIxR&quot;&gt;Download the letters here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Obsolete formats</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/obsolete-formats"/>
   <updated>2014-01-11T23:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/obsolete-formats</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mya41bJ0G71rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obsolete formats&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Faith, Hope &amp; Love</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/level-collective-faith-hope-love"/>
   <updated>2014-01-11T05:50:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/level-collective-faith-hope-love</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/fhl-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Faith, Hope &amp;amp; Love Tshirt design &quot; class=&quot;w100&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A T-shirt design I did for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thelevelcollective.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Level Collective&lt;/a&gt;, an independent ethical clothing label based in Sheffield. They do some great work with a charity in Romania and make some quality clothing with a lot of thought put into it. You can buy my T-shirt &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thelevelcollective.co.uk/shop/faith_hope_love/&quot; title=&quot;The Level Collective Shop&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good to see it getting some love on Instagram:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/faith-hope-love.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/p/uEy6YTu-jb/&quot;&gt;@captainworrell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/faith-hope-love-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/p/tjx4dFR9pl&quot;&gt;@racquelmishel&lt;/a&gt; on Instagram&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/faith-hope-love-3.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thelevelcollective.com/rich-wells/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;Read more about the design&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mz6e65o6jT1rr6vpvo3_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thelevelcollective.co.uk/shop/faith_hope_love/&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;Buy a t-shirt&lt;/a&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Christmas Sketches</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/christmas-sketches"/>
   <updated>2013-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/christmas-sketches</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Every year on the Sunday before Christmas, my wife&amp;#8217;s parents invite all the elderly single people at their church to join them for a Christmas dinner. There&amp;#8217;s lots of sherry, laughter, stories being shared and helpings of bread and butter pudding being enjoyed (a desert they request every year!). It&amp;#8217;s great to join in with the fun and capture some of the incredible character of people who&amp;#8217;ve been around for a little while longer than me!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo92pA0Aj1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo92pA0Aj1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo92pA0Aj1rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo92pA0Aj1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot; class=&quot;w100&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Friendly faces at Sheffield Mencap</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/sheffield-mencap"/>
   <updated>2013-12-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/sheffield-mencap</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo8bq7v2o1rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the downsides of my kind of job is that I spend far too much time at a computer and not enough time exploring and meeting people. Today was a nice exception as I had the opportunity to visit one of our clients, a charity called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sheffieldmencap.org.uk/&quot;&gt;Sheffield Mencap&lt;/a&gt;. I spent a few hours with them, taking photos and seeing the work that they do, and I had a lot of fun on the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/sheffield-mencap.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo8bq7v2o1rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo8bq7v2o1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the time I was there I popped my head into the busy kitchen to check out the cookery classes, sat in on OAP bingo, watched some energetic lads play basketball (they were big posers!), looked in on a media session and spent some time in one of their art rooms. Everyone was in full Christmas swing, with turkey sandwiches, Bing Crosby on the tinny stereo and plenty of cheesy Christmas jumpers worn by the staff. I think it might be one of the most welcoming and friendly places I have ever been to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo8bq7v2o1rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo8bq7v2o1rr6vpvo9_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo8bq7v2o1rr6vpvo7_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myo8bq7v2o1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Daddy daycare</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/daddy-daycare"/>
   <updated>2013-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/daddy-daycare</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Last Summer I was given a great chance to start working four days a week so that I could spend time with a little bundle of energy called Sophie. As we embarked on our Daddy Day Care experiment my wife challenged me to try to do something different every week. The result has been recorded in Sophie&amp;#8217;s inimitable style &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myntk1WL331rr6vpvo2_r1_400.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myntk1WL331rr6vpvo3_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myntk1WL331rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blogging about and living Tuesdays in this way has reminded me that the places we explore the least are often the places on our own doorstep. My adventures with Sophie have taken us to new parts of our &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/post/57531872899/today-we-went-to-western-park-museum-with-our&quot;&gt;city&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/post/63485318066/oct-8th-2013&quot;&gt;countryside&lt;/a&gt;, we&amp;#8217;ve discovered giant &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/post/66786999931/burritos&quot;&gt;spoons&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/post/66786999931/burritos&quot;&gt;burritos&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/post/64800663015/ikea&quot;&gt;the joys of Ikea&lt;/a&gt; and managed to fit in a fair bit of &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/post/68907288358/endcliffe-park&quot;&gt;longboarding&lt;/a&gt; too! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myntk1WL331rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myntk1WL331rr6vpvo9_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myntk1WL331rr6vpvo7_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myntk1WL331rr6vpvo1_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myntk1WL331rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Art prints for Open Doors</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/society6-prints"/>
   <updated>2013-12-02T02:12:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/society6-prints</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mx6405nmks1rr6vpvo2_400.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mx6405nmks1rr6vpvo3_500.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mx6405nmks1rr6vpvo1_400.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I&amp;#8217;m selling a few art prints this month on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://society6.com/richwells&quot; title=&quot;Society 6&quot;&gt;Society6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Really impressed by how hassle free their service is- you just upload a few images and bam, they put it on cushions t-shirts and all manner of printed goods!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/society6.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All profits I make from this experiment will go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.opendoorsuk.org/&quot; title=&quot;Open Doors&quot;&gt;charity&lt;/a&gt;, and there&amp;#8217;s free shipping on the site until cyber Monday (which is today). &lt;a href=&quot;http://society6.com/richwells?promo=d7fc57&quot;&gt;Get involved!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Gerard the goat</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/gerard-the-goat"/>
   <updated>2013-11-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/gerard-the-goat</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my8cztgeHN1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I saw this cheeky chap at an alpaca farm outside of Sheffield. I know he&amp;#8217;s not an alpaca by the way- you had to pay to walk around a field to see those, and so we ended up going to the warm cafe instead. Made using Procreate on the iPad, which is excellent.  &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Buggy longboarding</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/buggy-longboarding"/>
   <updated>2013-11-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/buggy-longboarding</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mysmm4eZws1rr6vpvo1_500.gif&quot; class=&quot;w100&quot;/&gt;&lt;p&gt;My first cinemagraph! &lt;a href=&quot;http://dayoffwithsophie.tumblr.com/post/68907288358/endcliffe-park&quot;&gt;Longboarding in Endcliffe Park&lt;/a&gt; on my day off with Sophie. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Making art that no one sees</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/making-art-that-no-one-sees"/>
   <updated>2013-10-25T09:00:20+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/making-art-that-no-one-sees</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_muqb4nrTVw1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We recently got back from a two week holiday in Cornwall, and before we left, my wife and I decided to take a break from social media and emails. We removed from our phones all icons which spit out numbers in red dots and made a pact not to touch them until we got back. It&amp;#8217;s something we&amp;#8217;ve done on holidays before and have always found it refreshing to properly disconnect from what&amp;#8217;s going on at home and get some perspective. Recommend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What stood out to me this holiday was that I found it hard initially to stop thinking about &amp;#8216;sharing&amp;#8217; stuff. I&amp;#8217;m definitely not a social media addict, and I don&amp;#8217;t check everything all the time, but I realised that as someone who posts quite a lot of images, I regularly think &amp;#8216;how can I share this?&amp;#8217; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#8217;s not a bad question in itself, but it can be unhealthy if it&amp;#8217;s the main thing you have on your mind when you see something interesting. If you&amp;#8217;re looking at a breathtaking sunset and are thinking &amp;#8216;how can I Instagram this?&amp;#8217;, you&amp;#8217;re probably not enjoying the moment as much as you could be. And thinking too much about how people will react to your work before you&amp;#8217;ve even started, can be a real creativity killer. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So on this social media free holiday, I decided to make art that no one would see, to make drawings and paintings, and then throw them away. It was actually quite hard at first, I felt like I was &amp;#8216;wasting my time&amp;#8217; and being very unproductive, but after a while I learned to enjoy the process and found it life giving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/how-can-i-share-this.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I listened to music and wrote down thoughts and prayers, sometimes on top of each other. I reminded myself that God was watching, and could make sense of it all, even if I couldn&amp;#8217;t. And most of all I began to enjoy drawing again.  Shame I can&amp;#8217;t show you what I came up with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I&amp;#8217;m back into normal life it&amp;#8217;s a lot harder to make space for unproductive art. There are always more important things I should probably be doing. But when I do make some space I never regret it, and am always reminded why I enjoy what I do.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Cornish sailors</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/cornish-sailors"/>
   <updated>2013-10-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/cornish-sailors</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myohx7pdMV1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had my first trip to Devon and Cornwall this summer and visited the incredible village of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.clovelly.co.uk/village&quot;&gt;Clovelly&lt;/a&gt;. Walking the steep cobbled streets it&amp;#8217;s easy to imagine what life was like for a victorian sailor, setting off from this unique port ready to brave harsh the seas in the hope of a good catch.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Helping young people volunteer with vInspired</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/vinspired"/>
   <updated>2013-08-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/vinspired</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;At &lt;a href=&quot;http://yoomee.com&quot;&gt;Yoomee&lt;/a&gt; we work with lots of inspiring organisations. One of them is called vInspired. The name gives it away. They provide young people with opportunities to volunteer and support worthy causes in creative ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current &lt;a href=&quot;http://vinspired.com&quot;&gt;vinspired.com&lt;/a&gt; started as a simple prototype and has developed as we have been running co-creation workshops, user testing sessions and generally getting as many people involved in the process as we can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired.jpg&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-1.jpg&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-3.jpg&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-5.jpg&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-7.jpg&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-12.jpg&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-11.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-2.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-4.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-9.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-10.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-6.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/vinspired-8.jpg&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love projects like this where I can get stuck in, take photos, do research, meet people, sketch things, take photos, design things, code things and test things. Basically I love variety!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Planet Earth</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/planet-earth-sketches"/>
   <updated>2013-08-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/planet-earth-sketches</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myohjplgDj1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myohjplgDj1rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple of iPad drawings whilst watching a Planet Earth Amazon episode. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Gathering</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/the-gathering"/>
   <updated>2013-07-03T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/the-gathering</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mymo76G6MP1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Making fires with some blokes in a field near Swindon. Enjoyed spending time with my Father in law and a few blokes from his church at the CVM gathering.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Vicar clothes</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/vicar-clothes"/>
   <updated>2013-07-01T09:28:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/vicar-clothes</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My friend Rich got ordained yesterday in Doncaster Minster. &lt;span&gt;Here are a few photos of him in a dress. I designed his stole, which is the white thing that goes round the neck. As I mostly work on short-term web projects it was satisfying to design something that will potentially last a long time (I can&amp;#8217;t imagine it wearing out anyway…)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp9es3Ildz1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp9es3Ildz1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp9es3Ildz1rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I wanted the design to be simple and different to the swirly gold and red crosses that are the norm in vicar land, so I stuck with one line width and one colour. The words are Jesus&amp;#8217; from Mark 1:15, which are significant to Rich. &amp;#8216;Repent&amp;#8217; probably conjures up all kinds of negative thoughts, but in fact it&amp;#8217;s really positive. It just means &amp;#8216;turn around&amp;#8217;, something that we all need to do from time to time. The Christian faith is good news: God is closer than we think and we&amp;#8217;re called to turn around and believe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp9es3Ildz1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Instagram</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/recent-instagrams"/>
   <updated>2013-06-27T12:44:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/recent-instagrams</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few recent &lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/richwells&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Instagrams&lt;/a&gt;. Taken a lot more since getting an iphone 5. Also enjoying using the &lt;a href=&quot;http://vsco.co/vscocam&quot;&gt;vscocam app&lt;/a&gt; to edit photos on the go.  &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp295ohtmi1rr6vpvo1_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp295ohtmi1rr6vpvo2_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp295ohtmi1rr6vpvo3_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp295ohtmi1rr6vpvo4_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp295ohtmi1rr6vpvo6_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mp295ohtmi1rr6vpvo5_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Elefriends</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/elefriends"/>
   <updated>2013-06-26T12:44:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/elefriends</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/elefriends.jpg&quot; class=&quot;w100&quot;/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  One of the most rewarding and well-used projects I&#39;ve worked on at &lt;a href=&quot;http://yoomee.com&quot;&gt;Yoomee&lt;/a&gt;, Elefriends is an online community for people who struggle with mental health issues. A closed, safe space for people to be real and to support others.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Like &lt;a href=&quot;/blog/vinspired&quot;&gt;vInspired&lt;/a&gt;, we started this project as a small prototype and developed it gradually over time, testing, learning and making it better. I was involved with design, UX and front-end build.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Here&#39;s a little introduction to Elefriends, narrated by Stephen Fry:
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;div class=&#39;fitvids&#39;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&#39;//player.vimeo.com/video/60585844&#39; width=&#39;500&#39; height=&#39;281&#39; frameborder=&#39;0&#39; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://elefriends.org.uk/&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;visit elefriends.org.uk&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;
    Also, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theguardian.com/society/christmas-charity-appeal-2014-blog/2014/dec/05/-sp-elefriends-the-social-network-for-the-mental-health-community&quot; target=&quot;blank&quot;&gt;here&#39;s an article &lt;/a&gt; about Elefriends in the Guardian.
  &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Castle market</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/castle-market"/>
   <updated>2013-05-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/castle-market</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my89ngZoAm1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Castle Market is such an interesting place to draw and look around. It&#39;s pretty grim, and I&#39;m sure the new Moor Market will be a much nicer shopping experience but I&#39;ll miss this place when it&#39;s gone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Broomhill</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/rooftops-of-broomhill-on-a-windy-day"/>
   <updated>2013-04-27T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/rooftops-of-broomhill-on-a-windy-day</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my89kvEEEQ1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rooftops of Broomhill, on a windy day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>George Senior &amp; Sons</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/george-senior-and-sons"/>
   <updated>2013-04-17T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/george-senior-and-sons</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my89iepJqK1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&quot;George Senior &amp;amp; Sons.&quot; An entrance from another era, now the side entrance to Ponds Forge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Tap</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/the-sheffield-tap"/>
   <updated>2013-04-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/the-sheffield-tap</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my89cymZcf1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Sheffield Tap, probably the best railway station pub in the country in my opinion. Also the closest to where we work. Need to do some sketches of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.guardian.co.uk/uk/the-northerner/2013/mar/20/sheffield-pubs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;inside&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; at some point.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Ingles' house</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/the-ingles"/>
   <updated>2013-04-03T21:13:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/the-ingles</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A while back my friend Gaz approached me and asked if I would paint a picture of his house with words on top of it. Not what I normally do but I had some free time and thought I’d say yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/the-ingles.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Painting/collage for the Ingles&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The words are different Bible verses that mean something to them and are all kind of related to the house in some way. A while back they moved from a quite nice part of Sheffield to a fairly rough part of the city with an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.message.org.uk/category/eden/&quot;&gt;Eden team&lt;/a&gt;, and they do lots of great things with young people on the streets. An inspirational couple!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Elon Musk at sxsw</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/elon-musk-at-sxsw-ipad-sketchnotes"/>
   <updated>2013-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/elon-musk-at-sxsw-ipad-sketchnotes</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mycpd9AIDL1rr6vpvo1_1280.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My iPad sketchnotes from Elon Musk’s keynote talk at South by Southwest this year. Elon is behind Tesla Motors and Spacex and is a bit of a genius. Sad to hear that he doesn’t have time to spend with his kids.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Signs of South by Southwest</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/signs-of-south-by-southwest"/>
   <updated>2013-03-21T13:46:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/signs-of-south-by-southwest</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo9_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo7_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo10_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mk0upcGlaE1rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had a great time last week in Austin. Here&amp;#8217;s a site I built to log our tweets and instagrams &lt;a href=&quot;http://sxsw.yoomee.com&quot;&gt;sxsw.yoomee.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Swiss Miss' 11 Rules</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/tina-roth-eisenberg-%20at-sxsw"/>
   <updated>2013-03-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/tina-roth-eisenberg- at-sxsw</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mycpa5WphM1rr6vpvo1_1280.png&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My iPad sketchnotes from Tina Roth Eisenberg&amp;#8217;s keynote talk at South by Southwest.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Sunset over Higger Tor</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/sunset-over-higger-tor-in-the-peak-district"/>
   <updated>2013-02-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/sunset-over-higger-tor-in-the-peak-district</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my899imrJb1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sunset over Higger Tor in the Peak District.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Behind the Electricworks</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/behind-the-electricworks"/>
   <updated>2013-02-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/behind-the-electricworks</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my896pIbiB1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The view from the back of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://electric-works.net/&quot;&gt;electricworks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, the building that I work in. I often sit here and have my lunch when the sun’s out. It wasn’t yesterday, and the sleet made sure I didn’t stay out for too long.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Motore</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/nick-from-motore-cafe"/>
   <updated>2013-02-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/nick-from-motore-cafe</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my890wRPOk1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nick from Motore Café by the station. Best coffee in Sheffield!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Winter Gardens</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/late-afternoon-in-the-winter-gardens"/>
   <updated>2013-01-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/late-afternoon-in-the-winter-gardens</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my86uuvx8B1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Late afternoon in the winter gardens, just as the sun was setting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Ruskin park</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/man-and-his-dog-in-ruskin-park"/>
   <updated>2013-01-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/man-and-his-dog-in-ruskin-park</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my86kpWS2S1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Man and his dog in Ruskin Park.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Sheffield in the snow</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/sheffield-in-the-snow"/>
   <updated>2013-01-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/sheffield-in-the-snow</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mymowwdjZI1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sheffield in the snow. Snapped this on my walk to work. No cycling in this weather!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>People watching at Caffe Nero</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/people-watching-at-caffe-nero"/>
   <updated>2013-01-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/people-watching-at-caffe-nero</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my869z9Ubq1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my869z9Ubq1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my869z9Ubq1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sketching at Caffe Nero in the winter gardens with the Sketchcrawl guys.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Park Hill flats just as the snow came</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/park-hill-flats-just-as-the-snow-came"/>
   <updated>2013-01-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/park-hill-flats-just-as-the-snow-came</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my85wdSSXu1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Procreate</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/a-few-procreate-ipad-paintings-i-received-an"/>
   <updated>2013-01-10T12:21:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/a-few-procreate-ipad-paintings-i-received-an</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgf6w0ruJ81rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgf6w0ruJ81rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgf6w0ruJ81rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgf6w0ruJ81rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My favourite iPad art app at the moment is Procreate. Love how easy it is to create textures and  colours. Here are a few quick doodles/paintings.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Bible Challenge Book</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/bible-challenge-book"/>
   <updated>2013-01-10T08:22:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/bible-challenge-book</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids&quot;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/53417575?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; title=&quot;100 Day Bible Challenge Book&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A while ago I got involved with a project called the &lt;a href=&quot;http://art.100daybiblechallenge.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;100 Day Bible Challenge&lt;/a&gt;, where I did an illustration a day for 100 days inspired by the Bible. It was a spare-time mini design marathon, and I learned a lot in the process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I finally got round to getting a prototype book printed of the artwork, which arrived the other day. During the challenge, one of the things that kept me going was the thought of having something nice to go on my coffee table at the end of it, so it’s really satisfying to have the first printed copy in my hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-1.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-2.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-3.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-4.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-5.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-6.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-7.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-8.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-9.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-10.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-3&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/100dbc-book-11.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;I used blurb for printing the book, and I’m pleased with the quality. However I’m looking to get it published to bring the costs down. Blurb is great for one-offs but at £45 a go, the book is far too expensive for anyone else to want to buy. I didn’t start out on this project to make money (I decided to &lt;a href=&quot;http://art.100daybiblechallenge.com/&quot; title=&quot;download the artwork&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;give away the artwork for free here&lt;/a&gt;), but I would love to have a book that other people can own, and something that I can afford to give away to people around me. Getting it printed in a larger run would help me achieve this, so if you know anyone who could help, please get in touch. (rich@yoomee.com)&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A walk through the Botanical Gardens</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/a-walk-through-the-botanical-gardens"/>
   <updated>2013-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/a-walk-through-the-botanical-gardens</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_my85dv11B91rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Mat</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/mat"/>
   <updated>2012-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/mat</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myohrk2wtq1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>From the sketchbook</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/from-the-sketchbook"/>
   <updated>2012-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/from-the-sketchbook</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo7_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo10_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo9_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoi9ch0vT1rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the sketchbook.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Father forgive</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/father-forgive"/>
   <updated>2012-11-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/father-forgive</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_myoh8pki8K1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>In Place of War branding</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/in-place-of-war"/>
   <updated>2012-10-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/in-place-of-war</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ipow.gif&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introducing Sophie</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/sophie-wells"/>
   <updated>2012-09-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/sophie-wells</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids wide&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/49013771?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; title=&quot;Sophie the sloth&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first few days of life with our little girl&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>China</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/china"/>
   <updated>2012-04-16T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/china</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids wide&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/40372602?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; title=&quot;China&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few months ago we went to China. We travelled around the country with some amazing people and got to experience so many new sights, smells and tastes. I shot way too much video but have finally got round to making a summary of one second shots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Music is &amp;#8216;Same Dream China&amp;#8217; by Gold Panda (&lt;a href=&quot;http://itunes.apple.com/gb/album/same-dream-china/id394131664?i=394131677&quot;&gt;buy on iTunes&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Yoomee goes Southwest</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/sxsw12"/>
   <updated>2012-03-29T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/sxsw12</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/39057126?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; title=&quot;Yoomee at SXSW 2012&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A video I made of our trip to SXSW in Austin last week. A roundup of our tweets and instagrams can be found &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://sxsw.yoomee.com/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Dan Mangan Tshirt designs</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/dan-mangan"/>
   <updated>2012-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/dan-mangan</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I did a few tshirt designs a while back for Canadian singer songwriter &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.danmanganmusic.com/&quot; title=&quot;Dan Mangan&quot;&gt;Dan Mangan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Here they are, in need of an iron. If you&amp;#8217;d like one, he has a few left in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.galleryac.com/merchandise/oh-fortune-t-shirt.html&quot; title=&quot;dan&#39;s shop&quot;&gt;his shop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewdbpoXG1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewdbpoXG1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewdbpoXG1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Terracotta Army</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/terracotta-army"/>
   <updated>2011-12-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/terracotta-army</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mymoidF3Qu1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tourists and two thousand year old soldier. A photo I took on our trip to the Terracotta Army.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>100 Day Bible Challenge</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/100daybiblechallenge"/>
   <updated>2011-11-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/100daybiblechallenge</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I&amp;#8217;ve been involved in a project at my church called 100 Day Bible Challenge. We&amp;#8217;re currently reading through 100 key parts of the Bible every day for 100 days and I am hoping to do a bit of daily artwork inspired by what we&amp;#8217;ve read. Its been great so far- we have 360 people on the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.facebook.com/groups/286637061359303&quot;&gt;Facebook group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and loads of discussions going on. Check the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://100daybiblechallenge.com/&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for more details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo1_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo7_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo9_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfirgt0vH1rr6vpvo10_r2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Download my free font Ello Ello</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/download-elloello-font"/>
   <updated>2011-11-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/download-elloello-font</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/ello-ello.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to write like me? Now you can. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/downloads/elloello.zip&quot; title=&quot;Download elloello!&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;Download ElloEllo here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p3&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;Licensed under a &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Ndsm Wharf, Amsterdam</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/ndsm-wharf"/>
   <updated>2011-09-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/ndsm-wharf</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;grid wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;col-1-2&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The NDSM Wharf is a really cool place that has an old Shipyard building warehouse, which has been transformed into a skatepark and customised portacabins for 250+ artists. It&amp;#8217;s a really interesting/inspiring/random place to walk around if you are ever in Amsterdam.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo2_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo10_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo8_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo9_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo11_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgewmzJVf41rr6vpvo12_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Picnic Festival</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/picnic11"/>
   <updated>2011-09-21T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/picnic11</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some photos I took from Picnic 11 in Amsterdam. The theme this year was &amp;#8216;Future cities- exploring global urbanisation and its impact on our cities, our societies and our lives.&amp;#8217; At Yoomee we developed the online networking tools and apps for the Festival, and it was reward to see it used by so many people over the week.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo3_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo4_r1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo7_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo9_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgfkqshvy21rr6vpvo10_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Les Alpes</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/les-alpes"/>
   <updated>2011-07-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/les-alpes</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids wide&quot;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/26984839?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; title=&quot;Les Alpes&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A video of our trip to the French Alps, where we cycled, drank coffee, fell off our bikes (well, just Jon) and watched the Tour de France.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Peace in the Park</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/peace-in-the-park"/>
   <updated>2011-06-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/peace-in-the-park</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids wide&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/24719761?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; title=&quot;Peace in the park balloon release&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Saturday Bry and myself manned the balloon stall at Peace in the Park, Sheffield. The idea was to get people to write messages of peace, attach them to helium balloons and release them all together at 5pm. After a few sketchy moments transporting them across a field under a net we managed to do just that. It all turned out a bit sony bravia&amp;#8230;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Holiday sketches</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/holiday-sketches"/>
   <updated>2011-06-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/holiday-sketches</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmb5kgxVq1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Some sketches I did last week whilst on holiday. Enjoyed getting away from emails and the internet, I should do it more often! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Panasonic GF1</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/panasonic-gf1"/>
   <updated>2011-02-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/panasonic-gf1</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;fitvids wide&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&quot;//player.vimeo.com/video/20334460?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;225&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; title=&quot;Panasonic GF1 test&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;After saving up for a while I bought a Panasonic GF1 last week, with a 20mm pancake lens. Really enjoying using it- perfect balance of quality and portability and does great video too. This is a quick video I made in imovie. Apologies for the boring shaky close ups!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Lift 11</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/lift11"/>
   <updated>2011-02-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/lift11</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo1_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo2_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo3_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo4_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo5_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo7_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo8_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo6_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/tumblr_files/tumblr_mgmbkxPOnH1rr6vpvo9_1280.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Had a fun time this week attending &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://liftconference.com/lift11&quot; title=&quot;lift 11&quot;&gt;Lift11 conference&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in Geneva. I was involved as a visual recorder at a workshop, sketching ideas, and helping people to visualise concepts. Unfortunately I can&amp;#8217;t post any of my work (as everyone had to sign an NDA), but I did take some photos of my time there. Think I might have a break now from espresso, chocolate and cheese!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Lanterns</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/lanterns"/>
   <updated>2011-02-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/lanterns</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/lantern-1.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/lantern-2.jpg&quot;/&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Various logos</title>
   <link href="http://richwells.me/projects/various-logos"/>
   <updated>2011-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://richwells.me/projects/various-logos</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/life-church.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/haemnet4.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/study-yorkshire-2.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/piefighter.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/downloads/coffee-plus.jpg&quot;&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
